

# Kuljit Kaur



Montreal, QC \$\frac{1}{2}\$ 5146211008 \$\qquad \text{kuljit2602@gmail.com}\$

#### LINKS (

- https://www.linkedin.com/in/kuljit-kaur-82750b17b/
- https://github.com/kuljit1408

## PROFESSIONAL () **SUMMARY**

I have done Web Technologies and Programming In Montreal, QC, I have well knowledge about Web Programming and Development, I have done another Bachelor's Computer Applications from India. I have good knowledge about HTML5, CSS3, BootStrap, JavaScript and PHP. I have Six months **experience** as a **Front End Web Developer** Intern. I am passionate for Web Development and I am **self-motivated** and like to take challenges.

### SKILLS

- **Programming Languages**
- HTML5, CSS3
- Bootstrap
- JavaScript
- PHP, Laravel Framework
- C#, C++, C
- Java
- React.js
- **Development Software**
- Visual Studio Code, Visual studio Management Tools
- Microsoft SQL Management Studio, MySQL Workbench
- PhpMyAdmin
- Netbeans

- **Eclipse**
- Sublime Text Editor, Notepad++
- Word Press
- **Brackets**
- Excel
- **Other Important Software**
- XAMPP, WAMP
- Git Bash, Git Hub
- **Command Prompt**
- Agile, Agile Scrum
- Jira, Trello

#### WORK HISTORY

#### FRONT END WEB DEVELOPER INTERN

01/2021 to 03/2021

## **Any Global**

- Implemented websites and Landing pages from concept through development.
- Standardized all output with a new, **responsive**, and **strategy**.
- **Collaborated** with product **team members** to implement new **feature** developments.
- Technical Skills:- Html5, Css3, BootStrap, JavaScript and Animations.

## FRONT END WEB DEVELOPER INTERN

08/2020 to 10/2020

## **HR Superhero**

Creating **new features**, **functionality** and **capabilities** on the

- eCommerce sites using JavaScript, BootStrap, HTML and CSS.
- Recommending **solutions** for a streamlined, **user-friendly interface** the design team.
- Performing bug fixes and code reviews.
- Manage website development projects from initial design through implementation and completion.

#### **BUFFET ATTENDANT**

06/2020 to 09/2020

#### **Buffet Casa Corfu**

- Replenished hot and cold food table and stocked beverage dispensers, plates and utensils, and ice supply.
- **Cleaned** food **preparation areas**, **tools** and **equipment**.
- Assisted guests, including offering personable greetings and taking orders.
- **Loaded food**, dishes and utensils on carts and trays to transport from designated food preparation areas to designated tables.

#### CASHIER AND STOCK MANAGER

01/2020 to 04/2020

## Marché Pak Stop

- Helped customers complete purchases, locate items and join reward programs to **promote loyalty**, satisfaction and sales numbers.
- Promoted customer loyalty and consistent sales by delivering friendly service and knowledgeable assistance.
- Processed **POS transactions**, including **checks**, **cash** and **credit** purchases or refunds.

## MACHINE OPERATOR & PACKAGING, LACROIX 05/2019 to 09/2019

#### Lacroix

- Pack, weight, and label completed items.
- **Operate tools** in order to aid in the **manufacturing process**.
- Perform **periodic checks** on equipment and **solve problems** as detected.

## **EDUCATION** ()

**Programing And Web Technologies** 

03/2021

ISI, L'Institut Supérieurd'Informatique, Montreal, QC

**Bachelor's Computer Applications** 

05/2017

**GNDU**, India

#### LANGUAGES (

**English** Hindi Punjabi